<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Xia He-Bleinagel</title>
    <link>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Xia He-Bleinagel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Create a Free Custom Domain-based email address</title>
      <link>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/03/create-a-free-custom-domain-based-email-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/03/create-a-free-custom-domain-based-email-address/</guid>
      <description>Once I&amp;rsquo;ve established my personal website, the next step is to create a professional email address. The good news, you can create a custom email address with Zoho for free, which takes only 5 minutes to complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take A Break and Continue</title>
      <link>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/03/take-a-break-and-continue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/03/take-a-break-and-continue/</guid>
      <description>I took a break to reflect and recharge. ChatGPT is a powerful tool. But it can&amp;rsquo;t solve every problem. The panic I experienced was genuine, but taking a break allows me to move forward with renewed energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 4 Data Engineering Zoomcamp Notes: Analytics Engineering and dbt</title>
      <link>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/02/week-4-data-engineering-zoomcamp-notes-analytics-engineering-and-dbt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/02/week-4-data-engineering-zoomcamp-notes-analytics-engineering-and-dbt/</guid>
      <description>I had completed the analytics engineering bootcamp in Udemy. So data modelling and dbt are not new to me. In week 4, some interesting take-aways for me are the usage of dbt cloud and the software engineering best practices like modularity, portability, CI/CD, and documentation. Great course as usual from dezoomcamp!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 3 Data Engineering Zoomcamp Notes: Data Warehouse and BigQuery</title>
      <link>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/02/week-3-data-engineering-zoomcamp-notes-data-warehouse-and-bigquery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/02/week-3-data-engineering-zoomcamp-notes-data-warehouse-and-bigquery/</guid>
      <description>In week 3 we learned data warehouse and google Big Query. Some best practices like creating external table, partition and clustering tables are introduced. We can even do machine learning in Big Query.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 2 Data Engineering Zoomcamp Notes: Prefect</title>
      <link>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/02/week-2-data-engineering-zoomcamp-notes-prefect/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/02/week-2-data-engineering-zoomcamp-notes-prefect/</guid>
      <description>In week 2 we learned Prefect to manage our data flow. I like Prefect very much because it allows to use python to define tasks and flows. Very interesting topic to learn!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximizing Efficiency with ChatGPT: My Experience</title>
      <link>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/01/maximizing-efficiency-with-chatgpt-my-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/01/maximizing-efficiency-with-chatgpt-my-experience/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT is impressive. To maximize its potential and increase efficiency, here&amp;rsquo;s my advice based on my experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1 Data Engineering Zoomcamp Notes</title>
      <link>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/01/week-1-data-engineering-zoomcamp-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/01/week-1-data-engineering-zoomcamp-notes/</guid>
      <description>During week 1, participants learned how to build a data pipeline and retrieve and ingest data using Docker, Postgres, Docker-compose, Terraform and Google Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction of Google Analytics API</title>
      <link>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/01/introduction-of-google-analytics-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/01/introduction-of-google-analytics-api/</guid>
      <description>The Google APIs are effective tools for managing large or complex Google Analytics accounts. They allow developers to programmatically extract historical GA data or list all GA properties with custom dimensions, saving a tremendous amount of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Custom Domain For My Hugo Personal Website Hosted On Github Pages</title>
      <link>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/01/a-custom-domain-for-my-hugo-personal-website-hosted-on-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/01/a-custom-domain-for-my-hugo-personal-website-hosted-on-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>I bought a domain called xiahe-bleinagel.com on Amazon Route 53. I will show you how to setup in order to visit this custom domain correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS IAM Day 1</title>
      <link>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/01/aws-iam-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/01/aws-iam-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Do you ever think of getting AWS Cloud certificates? This is one of my 2023 resolutions. Let&amp;rsquo;s learn together. Day 1 is all about the best practices of AWS IAM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From A Stay-At-Home Mom To A Data Scientist</title>
      <link>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/01/from-a-stay-at-home-mom-to-a-data-scientist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2023/01/from-a-stay-at-home-mom-to-a-data-scientist/</guid>
      <description>Life goes up and down. Important is that you never give up. Everyone has a chance to achieve his/her goal. This is my story of how I got a tech job from a stay-at-home mom. Remember, you are the best.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a Personal Website With Hugo</title>
      <link>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2022/12/create-a-personal-website-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/2022/12/create-a-personal-website-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>I built a personal website with Hugo successfully. I want to write down some key points to share my learning experience. Hugo is a static site generator and super fast. We will build one site with a theme template in 10 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there, I&amp;rsquo;m Xia. As a member of the AI &amp;amp; Data Analytics team, my focus is on cloud applications, data management, automation solutions and AI. I consider myself to be a data generalist with knowledge and experience in various areas including:
Cloud, AWS, Google cloud Data engineering (Database), Analytics engineering (Data warehouse) Machine learning/ statistics modelling Natural language processing, AI Dashboard / BI Data collection or data tracking with Google Analytics Contact me</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact me</title>
      <link>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can get in touch with me via email and consult my professional profile on LinkedIn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xiahe-bleinagel.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy
Effective date: 2023-03-01
Our website is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide to us when you visit our website, and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.
Information we collect
We may collect personal information that you provide to us when you sign up for our newsletter or contact us through our website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
